First contact has been made. It's war.
Cosmic Sin is a science fiction, action,
adventure film directed by Edward Drake.
In the year 2524, four centuries after humans started colonizing the outer planets, retired General James Ford
gets called back into service when a hostile alien fleet attacks soldiers on a remote planet.
The threat against mankind soon escalates into an interstellar war as Ford and a team
of elite soldiers try to stop the imminent attack before it's too late.
James Ford, played by Bruce Willis.
Fiona Ardene, played by Adelaide Kane.
Gen. Eron Ryle, played by Frank Grillo.
Alex Loche, played by Lochlyn Munro.
Ltg. Tieve, played by Costas Mandylor.
Coco, played by Johnny Messner.
Cosmic Sin is a 2021 American science fiction
action film directed by Edward Drake.
The film stars Bruce Willis, Frank Grillo, Brandon
Thomas Lee, Corey Large, Perrey Reeves, C.J.
Perry, Lochlyn Munro, and Costas Mandylor.
Cosmic Sin was released in the United States on March 12, 2021, by Saban Films.
The film was panned by critics and at the 42nd Golden Raspberry Awards won the
award for "Worst Performance by Bruce Willis in a 2021 Movie".
The award was later rescinded following Willis's diagnosis of aphasia.
The film explores themes of space battle, space war,
space colony, alien contact, future war.
The tone is thought_provoking.